flashgamestudio.com 2017-07-12

# Flashgamestudio Privacy Policy

Flashgamestudio, and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is a list of the information we collect and why we collect it.

**_Public Forums And High Scores_**

> This site makes message boards and high score postings available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**_Advertisers_**

> We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).

**_External Links_**

> This site contains links to other sites. Flashgamestudio is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**_Children's Guidelines_**

> This site DOES NOT MEET the Online Privacy Protection Act guidelines. The following criteria are violated: This site allows children to post or distribute any personally identifiable information without first obtaining verifiable parental consent. This site does not provide children notice of what information is collected. This site does not encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online. This site does not allow the parent to obtain the information collected from the child and provide a way for the parent to prevent the future use of that information. 

**_Contacting the Web Site_**

> If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [peter@sess.net](mailto:peter@sess.net)

**BACK TO Flashgamestudio**

>
